

JUNG (DAVID) LEE

Full Stack Web Developer

DETAILS

16413 54th Ave W , Lynnwood, WA, 98037 jungdavidlee@gmail.com 206-331-9301

PROFILE

Currently enrolled in the University of WA Web Developer Bootcamp to learn new skills and achieve a Web Development Certificate. My primary work experience prior to web development has been 10+ years in sales and customer service. That consisted of working independently in a fast paced, demanding environment utilizing a variety of systems and web-based tools to research and quickly resolve customer issues. I also communicated effectively as a strong, collaborative team member while creating and maintaining trouble tickets, accurately recording problem/symptom, analysis performed, resolution, and other relevant information within multiple CRMs.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Event Coordinator, NWN Motorsports, Seattle, WA

JUNE 2012 - PRESENT

- Create and manage each event and handle all public affairs.
- Coordinate with other staff members to ensure a smooth event.
- Research other events to make certain our events were just as if not more successful.
- Develop new ideas and strategies to improve and optimize each event.

General Manager, TMS Performance, Kent, WA

MARCH 2017 - JULY 2020

- Deliver excellent service to ensure high levels of customer satisfaction.
- Create business strategies to attract new customers, expand store traffic, and enhance profitability.
- Respond to customer complaints and concerns in a professional manner.
- Develop and arrange promotional material and in-store displays.
- Prepare detailed reports on buying trends, customer requirements, and profits.
- Undertake store administration duties such as managing store budgets and updating financial records.
- Monitor inventory levels and order new items.

Account Advocate, CDK Global, Seattle, WA

JUNE 2015 - DECEMBER 2016

- Managed 40+ websites for GM dealerships. (Cadillac, Chevy, GMC)
- Communicated with dealer staff to build and manage full websites.
- Coordinated with other team members to work on strategies for dealership success.
- Consistently grew book of business to maximize revenue for CDK.
- Extensive knowledge of Salesforce CRM for efficiency on customer management.

Sales Team Lead, Independence Auto Center, Everett, WA

MARCH 2012 - JUNE 2015

- Averaged 11 cars/month 18% of the sales for the whole dealership per month.
- Helped teammates become more efficient at follow up through Autoraptor CRM.
- Closed deals for teammates and assisted when necessary.
- Communicated with sales and service to ensure a seamless car delivery for clients.

EDUCATION

Certificate, UW Full Stack Web Developer Bootcamp, Seattle, WA

DECEMBER 2020 - JUNE 2021

This bootcamp provides education in the following: HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, jQuery, Express.js, React.js, Node.js, progressive web apps, agile methodology, computer science, database theory, MongoDB, MySQL, and Git.

	LI	IN	ΙK	S
--	----	----	----	---

LinkedIn GitHub

SKILLS

Fast Learner	Adaptability	
Communication Skills	Ability to Work Under Pressure	
Ability to Work in a Team	Creative Problem Solving	
CRM Systems	Web Development	
HTML/CSS/JavaScript	Git	
Bootstrap	jQuery	

REFERENCES

Node.js

Mookie Dedic from NWN Motorsports - GM nwnmotorsports@yahoo.com | 425-273-6831

Salem Elkabule from T-Mobile - Data Analyst s3000ly@yahoo.com | 425-433-3398

Aziz Hakim from Lexus of Bellevue - Technician azizhakims13@gmail.com | 206-851-8749